We are indecisive.
We are a trivial relationship.
There are no highlights in this life.
Listening to the sound of the waves at night doesn't suit us.
Let's put our thoughts on the wind.
I will meet you in the future.
Let's love useless things. We don't have the time to think about the meaning.
You are mine. We love each other.
We mimic what we desire.
Love me as it is.
You are mine. We wander in the evening.
At your signal, let's go beyond the dreams that color this world.
I just want to live freely.
Only my growing desire exists.
The wounds increase because of my mistake.
That doesn't lead to my confidence.
Your figure is shining as if a flower opens.
It shines like a beautiful moon.
Let's love useless things. We don't have enough time to think about the meaning.
You are mine. We love each other.
We mimic what we desire.
Love me as it is.
You are mine. We wander in the evening.
At your signal, let's go beyond the dreams that color this world.
I will add a color that suits you.
I am in an ambiguous state.
I make. Go to the future without the correct answer.
Go beyond your dreams.
I will add a color that suits you.
I want to be ambiguous.
I make. Go to the future without the correct answer.
Go beyond your dreams.